HUSEIN FADHLULLAH

PRODUCT MANAGEMENT / EX-TRAVEL MANAGER

+6285155159094 huseinfadhlullah@gmail.com Jatisampurna, Kota Bekasi, Jawa Barat 17435

SUMMARY

I love product development where you can dig into customer problems and solve them with modern tech. In product division i gather user requirements, create product backlog item, create UX design, helped launch new products and 50+ improvements. I'm also have 6+ years experiences as a travel manager who maintain relationships with 15 client groups, negotiate prices with travel agent around the world, create flyer design, and prepare all travel-related documentation. Love to learn anything that's new and useful for me. Seeking a career position to further develop expertise and experience in product management or travel industry.

EXPERIENCE

PT. Hijau Naavee Ideatama

Product Management

Jakarta Selatan Jul 2021 - Present

- Facilitated an agile environment, working across 3 teams to launch product features and improvements based on user requirements
- Analyze user pain points to address in product development, successfully resolving issues that increased user satisfaction across 3 companies
- Create product backlog items from the results of gathering user requirements phase
- Update upcoming features to product roadmap and validate with users
- Worked with tech lead to prioritize product features and improvements
- Working across other teams (design, software engineers) to conduct a product refinement
- Helped QA team to create a test case & scenarios
- Create product onboard and deliver it to the CS team & marketing team

Thiz Digital Marketing

Freelance

Remote

Jun 2021 - Present

- Built 3+ websites using wordpress CMS
- Designed 5+ wireframes and mockups to customers
- Optimize content for the website and social media platforms
- Designed 25+ digital flyer and brochure for promotional marketing
- Set up 2 brand new logo
- Directed a promotional videos that made a 1.000 views on youtube

PT. Citra Nashwa Indah Jaya Wisata

Travel Manager

Jakarta Selatan Feb 2017 - Dec 2022

- Maintaining positive relationships with 9+ vendors of direct travel, such as tour agents, car rentals, hotels, and airlines
- Negotiating preferred rates with 3+ vendors
- Planning travel accommodations, booking flights, hotels, car rentals, and coordinating activities
- Managed all travel documentation, including itineraries, visas and other personal documents

PT. Citra Nashwa Indah Jaya Wisata

IT Administrator

Jakarta Selatan Feb 2016 - Feb 2017

- Setting up 4 hardware and installing and configure software and drivers
- Update 10+ packages per month using internal content management system
- Maintaining and repairing 4 hardware or any peripheral devices

EDUCATION

Magister of Information System Management

Sep 2021

Binus University

Information System

Feb 2017

Binus University

SKILLS

Technical: Product management, UI & UX design, quality assurance, SQL, VS code, Product Growth.

Equipped: Agile methodology, good teamwork, product management, UX design, ERP knowledge, sales, photography, digital marketing, entrepreneur.

Tools: MS office, figma, adobe, git, slack, confluence, jira, asana, lightroom, google analytics.